Guide to the Agenda Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Production Files, 1969-1984; Series II; 4; (8 boxes)
  - Volume 14, Number 3 (Criticism Issue)
    - Proof, corrected, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2238-2239)
  - Volumes 14-15, Numbers 4-1
    - Advertising copy, contents page and related material, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2240)
    - Galley, corrected, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2241)
    - Proof, corrected, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2242)
    - Proof, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2243)
  - Volume 15, Numbers 2-3 (Myth and Twentieth Century Poetry)
    - Cover page, advertising copy and related material, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2244)
    - Proofs, corrected, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2245)
    - Proofs, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2246)
  - Volume 15, Number 4 (French Poetry Issue)
    - Contents page, advertising copy and related material, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2247)
    - Galley, corrected, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2248)
    - Proofs, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2249)
  - Volume 16, Number 1
    - Notes and related material, typescript, undated (Box 36, Folder 2250)
    - Galley, corrected, [1978] (Box 36, Folder 2251)
    - Galley, [1978] (Box 36, Folder 2252)
    - Proofs, corrected, [1978] (Box 36, Folder 2253-2254)
  - Volume 16, Numbers 3-4 (Classical Issue)
    - Contents page and related material, 1978-79 (Box 36, Folder 2255)
    - Galley, 1978-79 (Box 36, Folder 2256)
    - Proof, 1978-79 (Box 36, Folder 2257)
  - Volume 17, Number 1
    - Contents page and related material, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 2258)
    - Galley [incomplete], [1979] (Box 36, Folder 2259)
    - Proof, corrected, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 2260)
    - Proof, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 2261)
  - Volume 17, Number 2
    - Contents page and title page, [1979] (Box 36, Folder 2262)
    - Galley, corrected, with notes, [1979] (Box 36, Folder 2263)
  - Volumes 17-18, Numbers 3-1
    - Contents page and related material, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 2264)
    - Galley [incomplete], [1979-80] (Box 36, Folder 2265)
    - Proof, corrected, [1979-80] (Box 37, Folder 2266)
    - Proof, [1979-80] (Box 37, Folder 2267)
  - Volume 18, Number 2
    - Notes and related material, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2268)
    - Proofs, corrected, [1980] (Box 37, Folder 2269)
  - Volume 18, Number 3 (Robert Lowell Isssue)
    - Notes and related material, [1980] (Box 37, Folder 2270)
    - Galley, corrected, [1980] (Box 37, Folder 2271)
    - Proof, corrected, [1980] (Box 37, Folder 2272)
  - Volumes 18-19, Numbers 1-4 (Drama Issue)
    - Contents page and related material, [1981] (Box 37, Folder 2273)
    - Galley [incomplete], [1981] (Box 37, Folder 2274)
    - Proof, [1981] (Box 38, Folder 2275)
  - Volume 20, Number 2
    - Contents page and related material, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2276)
    - Galley, corrected, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2277)
    - Proofs, corrected, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2278)
  - Volume 20, Numbers 3-4 (Chinese Poetry Issue)
    - Contents page, [1982-83] (Box 38, Folder 2279)
    - Galley, corrected, [1982-83] (Box 38, Folder 2280)
    - Photographs of Chinese paintings [10 photographs], [1982-83] (Box 38, Folder 2281)
  - Volume 21, Number 3
    - Galley, with notes [incomplete], [1983] (Box 38, Folder 2282)
    - Proof, corrected, [1983] (Box 38, Folder 2283)
  - Volumes 21-22, Numbers 4-1 (Stanley Burnshaw Special Issue)
    - Contents page and related material, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 2284)
    - Proof, corrected, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 2285)
    - Proof, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 2286)
  - Volume 22, Number 2
    - Galley, corrected [incomplete], [1984?] (Box 38, Folder 2287)
    - Proof [incomplete], [1984?] (Box 38, Folder 2288)
  - Volume 22, Numbers 3-4
    - Galley, with corrections and notes to the printer, [1984] (Box 38, Folder 2289-2290)
    - Galley, with corrections and notes to the printer, [1984] (Box 39, Folder 2291)
    - Galley, corrected [incomplete], [1984] (Box 39, Folder 2292)
    - Proof, corrected, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 2293-2294)
    - Proof, [1984] (Box 39, Folder 2295)
  - Miscellaneous notes and fragments relating to Ezra Pound, undated (Box 39, Folder 2296)
  - Miscellaneous notes and fragments, 1964, undated (Box 39, Folder 2297)
- Correspondence, 1958-1985; Series III; 6.5; (13 boxes)
  Series III, Correspondence, is arranged alphabetically by name. Four folders of chronologically arranged unidentified correspondence can be found at the end of the series.
  - "Aa-Ag" general, 1959-85 (Box 40, Folder 2298)
  - "Ah-Am" general, 1967-75 (Box 40, Folder 2299)
  - "An-Ap" general, 1959-78 (Box 40, Folder 2300)
  - "Aq-Az" general, 1961-82 (Box 40, Folder 2301)
  - Aldington, Richard, 1959 Apr 21 (Box 40, Folder 2302)
  - Alexander, Michael, 1963-84, undated (Box 40, Folder 2303-2309)
  - Alvarez, Alfred, undated (Box 40, Folder 2310)
  - Alwyn, William, 1962-78 (Box 40, Folder 2311)
  - The Arts Council of Great Britain, 1963-82, undated (Box 40, Folder 2312-2318)
  - Awiszus, Sabine, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2319)
  - "Ba" general, 1959-84 (Box 40, Folder 2320)
  - "Be" general, 1959-82 (Box 40, Folder 2321)
  - "Bf-Bi" general, 1959-83 (Box 40, Folder 2322)
  - "Bj-Bl" general, 1959-78 (Box 40, Folder 2323)
  - "Bm-Br" general, 1964-82 (Box 40, Folder 2324)
  - "Bu" general, 1959-81 (Box 40, Folder 2325)
  - Bantock, Gavin, 1965-78 (Box 40, Folder 2326)
  - Bayley, John, 1963-83, undated (Box 40, Folder 2327)
  - Beckett, Samuel, 1981 Jul 28 (Box 40, Folder 2328)
  - Bedford, William, 1973-84, undated (Box 40, Folder 2329-2330)
  - Bergonzi, Bernard, 1969 Dec 27 (Box 40, Folder 2331)
  - Berryman, John, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 2332)
  - Betjeman, John, 1959, undated (Box 41, Folder 2333)
  - Birney, Earle, 1963-71, undated (Box 41, Folder 2334)
  - Blackburn, Thomas, undated (Box 41, Folder 2335)
  - Blackwell's Booksellers (Oxford), 1963-65, undated (Box 41, Folder 2336)
  - Blamires, David, 1966-83 (Box 41, Folder 2337)
  - Bloodaxe Books, 1979-84 (Box 41, Folder 2338)
  - Bly, Robert, 1959-76, undated (Box 41, Folder 2339)
  - Bold, Alan, 1968-69 (Box 41, Folder 2340)
  - Bonnerot, Louis, 1960-74 (Box 41, Folder 2341)
  - Bosley, Keith, 1970-77 (Box 41, Folder 2342)
  - Bridson, D. G., 1969-80 (Box 41, Folder 2343)
  - Bridson, Joyce T., 1983 Oct 23 (Box 41, Folder 2344)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1967-81 (Box 41, Folder 2345)
  - Brown, Gordon, D., 1970-82 (Box 41, Folder 2346)
  - Brownjohn, Alan, 1968-84 (Box 41, Folder 2347)
  - Bruce, Sylvia, 1967-68 (Box 41, Folder 2348)
  - Buck, Heather, 1976-83 (Box 41, Folder 2349)
  - Bunting, Basil, 1969-81, undated (Box 41, Folder 2350)
  - Burns, T. F., 1967-78 (Box 41, Folder 2351)
  - "Ca-Cam" general, 1966-81 (Box 41, Folder 2352)
  - "Car-Ce" general, 1964-76 (Box 41, Folder 2353)
    See also: Oversize, Box 57, folder 2787
  - "Ch-Ci" general, 1960-84 (Box 41, Folder 2354)
  - "Cl" general, 1959-80 (Box 41, Folder 2355)
  - "Coa-Com" general, 1964-84 (Box 41, Folder 2356)
  - "Con-Cot" general, 1959-82 (Box 41, Folder 2357)
  - "Cp-Cz" general, 1963-84 (Box 41, Folder 2358)
  - Car, M., 1963-65 (Box 41, Folder 2359)
  - Carcanet Press, 1963-84 (Box 41, Folder 2360-2361)
  - Carroll, Eugene, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 2362)
  - Carter, Tom, 1959-63 (Box 41, Folder 2363)
  - Cayley, John H., 1981-82 (Box 41, Folder 2364)
  - Clark, Kenneth, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2365)
  - Clothier, Cal, 1967-72 (Box 41, Folder 2366)
  - Clucas, Humphrey, 1980-81, undated (Box 41, Folder 2367)
  - Cocteau, Jean (Secretary), 1959 Mar 9 (Box 41, Folder 2368)
  - Coghill, Nevill, 1963, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2369)
  - Collier, Michael, 1971-84 (Box 42, Folder 2370)
  - Cookson, William, 1958-83, undated (Box 42, Folder 2371-2374)
  - Cole, Thomas, 1959-67 (Box 42, Folder 2375)
  - Conquest, Robert, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 2376)
  - Co-operative Bank, Limited, 1973-79 (Box 42, Folder 2377)
  - Cooper, Arthur, 1974-84 (Box 42, Folder 2378-2379)
  - Corcoran, John, 1974-80 (Box 42, Folder 2380)
  - Cox, Kenneth, 1966-79 (Box 42, Folder 2381)
  - Cournos, John, 1962-64, undated (Box 42, Folder 2382)
  - Creeley, Robert, 1965-79 (Box 42, Folder 2383)
  - Cummings, E. E., 1959 (Box 42, Folder 2384)
  - "Da" general, 1959-83 (Box 42, Folder 2385)
  - "De" general, 1958-79 (Box 42, Folder 2386)
  - "Di" general, 1973-83 (Box 42, Folder 2387)
  - "Do-Dy" general, 1958-82 (Box 42, Folder 2388)
  - D'Arcy, Martin, S. J., 1966 Sep 10 (Box 42, Folder 2389)
  - Dale, Peter, undated (Box 42, Folder 2390-2391)
  - Davenport, Guy, 1959-70 (Box 42, Folder 2392)
  - Davie, Donald, 1965-71 (Box 42, Folder 2393-2395)
  - Davies, Aneirin Talfan, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 2396)
  - Dekker, George, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 2397)
  - Denis, Hayes, and Company, 1976-77 (Box 42, Folder 2398)
  - Dent, Peter, 1965-83, undated (Box 42, Folder 2399-2400)
  - Dickey, James, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 2401)
  - Dondo, Mathurin, 1961-63 (Box 42, Folder 2402)
  - Drummond, John, 1970-71 (Box 42, Folder 2403)
  - du Sautoy, Peter, 1978-82 (Box 42, Folder 2403a)
  - Duncan, Robert, 1965-66 (Box 42, Folder 2404)
  - Duncan, Ronald, 1961-72 (Box 42, Folder 2405-2406)
  - Dunn, Douglas, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2407)
  - "Ea-Ed" general, 1959-85 (Box 43, Folder 2408)
  - "Eh-Ey" general, 1959-79 (Box 43, Folder 2409)
  - Eagleton, Terry, 1975-76 (Box 43, Folder 2410)
  - Ede, H. S., 1966 (Box 43, Folder 2411)
  - Empson, William, 1962-63 (Box 43, Folder 2412)
  - Encounter
    See: Stephen Spender, Box 50 folder 2648
  - "Fa" general, 1965-67 (Box 43, Folder 2413)
  - "Fe-Fo" general, 1959-84 (Box 43, Folder 2414)
  - "Fr-Fy" general, 1959-79 (Box 43, Folder 2415)
  - Faber and Faber, Limited, 1960-83, undated (Box 43, Folder 2416-2420)
  - Farley, Michael, 1983-84 (Box 43, Folder 2421)
  - Ferguson, Peter, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 2422)
  - Fiobenius, Sebastian, 1959-63 (Box 43, Folder 2423)
  - Fox, C. J., 1967-70, undated (Box 43, Folder 2424)
  - French, William, 1959, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 2425)
  - Fuller, John, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 2426)
  - Fuller, Roy, 1965-68, undated (Box 43, Folder 2427)
  - "Ga-Gl" general, 1959-79 (Box 43, Folder 2428)
  - "Go-Gra" general, 1959-83 (Box 43, Folder 2429)
  - "Gre-Gu" general, 1963-82 (Box 43, Folder 2430)
  - Gallup, Donald, 1963-70 (Box 43, Folder 2431)
  - Garnett, Anthony, 1974-81 (Box 43, Folder 2432)
  - Gascoyne, David, 1982-83 (Box 43, Folder 2433)
  - Giardelli, Arthur, 1967-77 (Box 43, Folder 2434)
  - Gibbons, Reginald, 1974-80 (Box 43, Folder 2435)
  - Goacher, Dennis, 1962-63, undated (Box 43, Folder 2436)
  - Gray, Nicolete, 1977, undated (Box 43, Folder 2437)
  - Greene, Jonathan, 1968-69 (Box 43, Folder 2438)
  - Grieve, Christopher
    See: Hugh MacDiarmid, Box 46 folder 2509-2510
  - Gunn, Thom, 1966-79 (Box 43, Folder 2439)
  - "Ha" general, 1958-81 (Box 44, Folder 2440)
  - "He" general, 1964-80 (Box 44, Folder 2441)
  - "Hi-Ho" general, 1964-85 (Box 44, Folder 2442)
  - "Hor-How" general, 1964-82 (Box 44, Folder 2443)
  - "Hub-Hum" general, 1964-81 (Box 44, Folder 2444)
  - "Hus-Hy" general, 1959-80 (Box 44, Folder 2445)
  - Hague, René, 1974-80, undated (Box 44, Folder 2446-2447)
  - Hall, Donald, 1960-80, undated (Box 44, Folder 2448)
  - Hamburger, Michael, 1964-81, undated (Box 44, Folder 2449)
  - Hamilton, Ian, 1963-68 (Box 44, Folder 2450)
  - Harewood, George, Earl of, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 2451)
  - Heaney, Seamus, 1984 Jul 9 (Box 44, Folder 2452)
  - Heath-Stubbs, John, 1961-81, undated (Box 44, Folder 2453)
  - Hefferman, Thomas, 1964-66 (Box 44, Folder 2454)
  - Hesse, Eva, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 2455)
  - Hill, Geoffrey, 1964-83 (Box 44, Folder 2456-2457)
  - Holmes, Richard, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 2458)
  - Homberger, Eric, 1969-73 (Box 44, Folder 2459)
  - Horovitz, Michael, 1962-84, undated (Box 44, Folder 2460)
  - Hughes, Ted, undated (Box 44, Folder 2461)
  - "I" general, 1963-75 (Box 44, Folder 2462)
  - Ismail, Jamila, 1970-73 (Box 44, Folder 2463)
  - "Ja-Je" general, 1964-81 (Box 44, Folder 2464)
  - "Jo" general, 1961-77 (Box 44, Folder 2465)
  - Jay, Peter, 1964-82, undated (Box 44, Folder 2466-2467)
  - John, Roland, 1973-81, undated (Box 44, Folder 2468)
  - Jones, David, 1960-63 (Box 44, Folder 2469)
  - Jordan, Clive, 1962-64 (Box 44, Folder 2470)
  - Julliard, René
    See: Dominique de Roux, Box 49 folder 2608
  - "Ka-Ke" general, 1959-80 (Box 44, Folder 2471)
  - "Kf-Kz" general, 1959-84 (Box 44, Folder 2472)
  - Kaufman, Wallace, 1964-66, undated (Box 45, Folder 2473)
  - Keeble, Brain, 1972-77, undated (Box 45, Folder 2474)
  - Kenner, Hugh, 1960-78 (Box 45, Folder 2475-2476)
  - Kermode, Frank, 1974-75 (Box 45, Folder 2477)
  - Kern, Robert, 1964-68 (Box 45, Folder 2478)
  - Kirkup, James, 1964 Mar 19 (Box 45, Folder 2479)
  - Kramer, Lotte, 1977-84 (Box 45, Folder 2480)
  - "La-Lad" general, 1959-81 (Box 45, Folder 2481)
  - "Lam-Law" general, 1959-78 (Box 45, Folder 2482)
  - "Le" general, 1967-81 (Box 45, Folder 2483)
  - "Li" general, 1963-82 (Box 45, Folder 2484)
  - "Lo-Ly" general, 1956-82 (Box 45, Folder 2485)
  - Larkin, Philip, 1976-77 (Box 45, Folder 2486)
  - Laughlin, James
    See: New Directions, Box 47 folder 2543-2547
  - Lehmann, John, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 2487)
  - Levertov, Denise, 1963, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 2488)
  - Levi, Peter, 1962-78, undated (Box 45, Folder 2489-2493)
    See also: Oversize, Box 57, folder, 2788
  - Lewis, Anne Wyndham, 1969, undated (Box 45, Folder 2494)
  - Lewis, C. S., 1963 (Box 45, Folder 2495)
  - Logue, Christopher, 1967-83 (Box 45, Folder 2496)
  - London Review
    See: Alan Ross, Box 49 folder 2607
  - Lowell, Robert, 1965-70 (Box 45, Folder 2497)
  - Lucie-Smith, Edward, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 2498)
  - "Mac" general, 1959-84 (Box 45, Folder 2499)
  - "Maf-Mal" general, 1963-73 (Box 45, Folder 2500)
  - "Man-Mar" general, 1959-81 (Box 45, Folder 2501)
  - "Mat-May" general, 1959-79 (Box 45, Folder 2502)
  - "Me-Mel" general, 1962-84 (Box 45, Folder 2503)
  - "Men-Met" general, 1967-74 (Box 45, Folder 2504)
  - "Mil" general, 1959-81 (Box 45, Folder 2505)
  - "Min-Mit" general, 1972-84 (Box 45, Folder 2506)
  - "Mo-Mor" general, 1959-77 (Box 45, Folder 2507)
  - "Mot-Mu" general, 1959-82 (Box 45, Folder 2508)
  - MacDiarmid, Hugh, 1960-78, undated (Box 46, Folder 2509-2510)
  - Makin, Peter, 1977-80 (Box 46, Folder 2511)
  - Malanga, Gerard, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 2512)
  - Martin, Seeker, and Warburg, Limited, 1980-81 (Box 46, Folder 2513)
  - Martinelli, Sheri, 1958-70, undated (Box 46, Folder 2514)
  - Massey, Alan, 1974-81 (Box 46, Folder 2515-2516)
  - May, Derwent, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 2517)
  - Meacham, Harry, 1959-68 (Box 46, Folder 2518)
  - Mermaid Theatre (London), 1973-74 (Box 46, Folder 2519)
  - Meschonnic, Henry, 1980 Mar 13 (Box 46, Folder 2520)
  - Methuen and Company, Limited, 1961-81 (Box 46, Folder 2521)
  - Meynell, Laurence, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 2522)
  - Michel, Caroline, 1977, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 2523)
  - Michel, Walter, 1968-69 (Box 46, Folder 2524)
  - Middleton, Christopher, 1965-73 (Box 46, Folder 2525)
  - Middleton, David, 1972-82 (Box 46, Folder 2526)
  - Miller, David, 1972-74 (Box 46, Folder 2527)
  - Milne, Evart, 1959-80, undated (Box 46, Folder 2528-2530)
  - Mitchinson, Naomi, 1963, 1979, undated (Box 46, Folder 2531)
  - Montague, John, 1967-73, undated (Box 46, Folder 2532)
  - Moody, A. D., 1976-80 (Box 46, Folder 2533)
  - Moore, Henry, 1961-67 (Box 46, Folder 2534)
  - Moore, Marianne, 1964-68 (Box 46, Folder 2535)
  - Motion, Andrew, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 2536)
  - Murdoch, Iris, undated (Box 46, Folder 2537)
  - "Na" general, 1961-80 (Box 46, Folder 2538)
  - "Ne" general, 1959-78 (Box 46, Folder 2539)
  - "Ni-No" general, 1962-81 (Box 46, Folder 2540)
  - Naylor, Margaret D., 1968-73 (Box 46, Folder 2541)
  - Neame, Alan, 1961-84 (Box 46, Folder 2542)
  - New Departures
    See: Michael Horovitz, Box 15 folder 1021
  - New Directions, 1960-82 (Box 47, Folder 2543-2547)
  - Niemojowski, Jerzy, 1959-69, undated (Box 47, Folder 2548)
  - Nye, Robert, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 2549)
  - "Oa-Op" general, 1963-77 (Box 47, Folder 2550)
  - "Or-Oz" general, 1959-84 (Box 47, Folder 2551)
  - Odlin, R., 1959-63 (Box 47, Folder 2552)
  - O'Driscoll, Dennis, 1980-81 (Box 47, Folder 2553)
  - O'Grady, Desmond, 1979-82 (Box 47, Folder 2554)
  - O'Higgins, Michael, 1959-84 (Box 47, Folder 2555)
  - Orr, Peter, 1974-77 (Box 47, Folder 2556)
  - Oxley, William, 1970-76 (Box 47, Folder 2557)
  - "Pa" general, 1962-81 (Box 47, Folder 2558)
  - "Pe-Ph" general, 1959-75 (Box 47, Folder 2559)
  - "Pi-Poe" general, 1960-84 (Box 47, Folder 2560)
  - "Pol-Pr" general, 1969-84 (Box 47, Folder 2561)
  - Paideuma, 1971-82, undated (Box 47, Folder 2562)
  - Palmer, Penelope, 1963-79 (Box 47, Folder 2563)
  - Passavant, Elise, undated (Box 47, Folder 2564)
  - Pearlman, Daniel, 1970-79 (Box 47, Folder 2565)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1959-74 (Box 47, Folder 2566)
  - Peck, John, 1970-84 (Box 47, Folder 2567-2568)
  - Penguin Books, 1962-71 (Box 48, Folder 2569)
  - Peter Owen, Ltd., 1959 (Box 48, Folder 2570)
  - Piggot, Stuart, 1966-75, undated (Box 48, Folder 2571)
  - Pinsky, Robert, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 2572)
  - Pinter, Harold, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 2573)
  - Poet, 1962, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 2574)
  - Porteus, Hugh Gordon, 1969-83, undated (Box 48, Folder 2575-2576)
  - Pound, Dorothy, 1960-73, undated (Box 48, Folder 2577-2585)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1959-71 (Box 48, Folder 2586)
  - Pound, Omar, 1958-82, undated (Box 48, Folder 2587)
  - Powell, Enoch, 1982-83 (Box 48, Folder 2588)
  - Pryce-Jones, David, undated (Box 48, Folder 2589)
  - "Q" general, 1972-77 (Box 48, Folder 2590)
  - Quartermain, Peter, 1977-78 (Box 48, Folder 2591)
  - Quinn, Mary Bernetta, 1964-75 (Box 48, Folder 2592)
  - "Ra" general, 1963-78 (Box 48, Folder 2593)
  - "Re" general, 1967-84 (Box 48, Folder 2594)
  - "Ri-Ro" general, 1959-80 (Box 48, Folder 2595)
  - "Ru" general, 1972-81 (Box 48, Folder 2596)
  - de Rachewiltz, Mary, 1971-83 (Box 48, Folder 2597)
  - Raine, Kathleen, 1971-82 (Box 49, Folder 2598)
  - Rainer, Dachine, 1972-84 (Box 49, Folder 2599)
  - Read, Herbert, 1959-68 (Box 49, Folder 2600)
  - Reck, Michael, 1966-70, undated (Box 49, Folder 2601)
  - Redgrove, Peter, 1975-77 (Box 49, Folder 2602)
  - Ricks, Christopher, 1975, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 2603)
  - Roethke, Beatrice, 1963-64 (Box 49, Folder 2604)
  - Rokeah, David, 1966-80 (Box 49, Folder 2605)
  - Rosenthal, Mack, 1967-84 (Box 49, Folder 2606)
  - Ross, Alan, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 2607)
  - Roux, Dominique de, 1964, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 2608)
  - Rudge, Olga, 1970-79 (Box 49, Folder 2609)
  - Rudolf, Anthony, undated (Box 49, Folder 2610)
  - Russell, Peter, 1959-85, undated (Box 49, Folder 2611-2612)
  - "Sa-Sc" general, 1958-75 (Box 49, Folder 2613)
  - "Se-Sh" general, 1964-84 (Box 49, Folder 2614)
  - "Si-Sk" general, 1965-81 (Box 49, Folder 2615)
  - "Sm-So" general, 1964-82 (Box 49, Folder 2616)
  - "Sp-Sr" general, 1961-73 (Box 49, Folder 2617)
  - "Sta" general, 1961-81 (Box 49, Folder 2618)
  - "Ste-Str" general, 1959-68 (Box 49, Folder 2619)
  - "Su" general, 1963-79 (Box 49, Folder 2620)
  - "Sw-Sz" general, 1963-77 (Box 49, Folder 2621)
  - St. James Press, 1968-74 (Box 49, Folder 2622)
  - Sala, Annamaria, 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 2623)
  - Sandars, Nancy K., 1966-83 (Box 49, Folder 2624)
  - Empty folder (Box 49, Folder 2625)
  - Schmidt, Michael, 1968-76, undated (Box 50, Folder 2626)
  - Scott, Alexander, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 2627)
  - Scott, Tom, 1963-83 (Box 50, Folder 2628-2631)
  - Scupham, Peter, 1974-75 (Box 50, Folder 2632)
  - Selerie, Gavin, 1962-80 (Box 50, Folder 2633)
  - Sexton, Anne, 1966-66 (Box 50, Folder 2634)
  - Seymour-Smith, Martin, 1969-72 (Box 50, Folder 2635)
  - Shulman and Partners, 1977-80 (Box 50, Folder 2636)
  - Silkin, John, 1969-83, undated (Box 50, Folder 2637-2638)
  - Singh, G., 1970-80 (Box 50, Folder 2639)
  - Sisson, Charles H., 1959-83 (Box 50, Folder 2640-2643)
  - Snodgrass, W. D., 1965-76 (Box 50, Folder 2644)
  - Snyder, Gary, 1968, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 2645)
  - Social Credit Association, 1959, undated (Box 50, Folder 2646)
  - Spann, Marcella, 1970-75 (Box 50, Folder 2647)
  - Spender, Stephen, 1963-65 (Box 50, Folder 2648)
  - Stafford, William, 1966-76 (Box 50, Folder 2649)
  - Stallworthy, Jon, 1966-82, undated (Box 50, Folder 2650)
  - Stock, Noel, 1961-69, undated (Box 50, Folder 2651)
  - Stoneburner, Tony, 1966-74 (Box 50, Folder 2652)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 2653)
  - Suter, Anthony, 1973-78 (Box 50, Folder 2654)
  - Sutton, Walter, 1963-65 (Box 50, Folder 2655)
  - Swabey, Henry, 1958-82, undated (Box 50, Folder 2656)
  - Sykes, Christopher, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 2657)
  - Symons, Julian, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 2658)
  - Sycamore Press
    See: John Fuller, Box 43 folder 2426
  - "Ta-Te" general, 1967-84 (Box 51, Folder 2659)
  - "Th" general, 1963-82 (Box 51, Folder 2660)
  - "Ti" general, 1961-80 (Box 51, Folder 2661)
  - "Tu-Tz" general, 1959-84 (Box 51, Folder 2662)
  - Tanner, Tony, undated (Box 51, Folder 2663)
  - Tarn, Nathaniel, 1963-68 (Box 51, Folder 2664)
  - Thames and Hudson, Limited, 1969-80 (Box 51, Folder 2665-2666)
  - Thomas, D. M., 1963-68 (Box 51, Folder 2667)
  - Thomas, R. S., 1965-66 (Box 51, Folder 2668)
  - Thompson, Peter, 1968-69 (Box 51, Folder 2669)
  - Thwaite, Anthony, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 2670)
  - The Times Literary Supplement, 1961-80, undated (Box 51, Folder 2671)
  - Tomlinson, Charles, 1961-84, undated (Box 51, Folder 2672-2675)
  - Turnbull, Gael, 1966-69 (Box 51, Folder 2676)
  - "Ua-Unic" general, 1963-84 (Box 51, Folder 2677)
  - "Univ" general, 1959-81 (Box 51, Folder 2678)
  - "V" general, 1967-82 (Box 51, Folder 2679)
  - Vassar College
    See: Eugene Carroll. Box 41 folder 2362
  - "Wa" general, 1960-81 (Box 51, Folder 2680)
  - "We" general, 1964-82 (Box 51, Folder 2681)
  - "Wh" general, 1963-80 (Box 51, Folder 2682)
  - "Wi" general, 1959-76 (Box 51, Folder 2683)
  - "Wl-Wy" general, 1959-80 (Box 51, Folder 2684)
  - Wade, Stephen, 1977-81, undated (Box 51, Folder 2685)
  - Wainwright, Jeffrey, 1974-78, undated (Box 51, Folder 2686)
  - Warner, Val, 1975-77 (Box 51, Folder 2687)
  - West, Rebecca, 1961-82 (Box 51, Folder 2688)
  - Wilcockson, Colin, 1975-84 (Box 51, Folder 2689-2690)
  - Williams, Jonathan, 1973-78 (Box 52, Folder 2691)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 2692)
    With: Construction, poem, typescript; The Painting, poem, typescript and The American Idiom, essay, mimeograph
  - Whigham, Peter, 1958-81, undated (Box 52, Folder 2693-2697)
  - Witemeyer, Hugh, 1973-83, undated (Box 52, Folder 2698)
  - Wright, David, 1961-81, undated (Box 52, Folder 2699-2700)
  - Wylie, Andrew, 1960-70, undated (Box 52, Folder 2701-2704)
  - "X-Z" general, 1959-81 (Box 52, Folder 2705)
  - Zukofsky, Louis, 1959-76 (Box 52, Folder 2706)
  - Unidentified, 1959-84, undated (Box 52, Folder 2707-2710)
- Additional Papers, 1914-1983; Series IV; 2; (4 boxes)
  Series IV, Additional Papers, is arranged topically, as follows: Business Papers, William Cookson, Photographs, and Printed Works.
  - Business Papers
    - Addresses, undated (Box 53, Folder 2711)
    - Advertising copy, 1967-79 (Box 53, Folder 2712)
    - Arts Council of Great Britain grant, 1970-81, undated (Box 53, Folder 2713-2714)
    - Bills, 1967-81 (Box 53, Folder 2715)
    - Checkbook registers, 1980-81 (Box 53, Folder 2716)
    - Credit and debit slips, 1980-81 (Box 53, Folder 2717)
    - Invoices, 1981-82 (Box 53, Folder 2718)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-81 (Box 53, Folder 2719-2720)
    - Orders, 1964-74 (Box 53, Folder 2721)
    - Permission to publish forms, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 2722)
    - Poets and Painters Press
      - Invoices, 1967-80 (Box 53, Folder 2723)
      - Press statements, 1967-80 (Box 53, Folder 2724)
    - Receipts, 1977-81 (Box 53, Folder 2725)
    - Remittance advice, 1981-82 (Box 53, Folder 2726)
    - Royalty statments, 1964-79 (Box 53, Folder 2727)
    - Statements, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 2728)